weltontrust.com 2017-04-01

# Welton: Privacy Policy

Welton Investment Partners believes that protecting the privacy of your nonpublic information is of utmost importance and, therefore, we are committed to maintaining the privacy of the nonpublic personal information we obtain from you and from other sources about you in the course of providing you with our products and services. Accordingly, we are providing you with the following information relating to Welton's Privacy Policy and Procedures.

**Information we collect and sources of information**

We may collect information about you to help identify you, evaluate your subscription, service and manage your investments in the products we sell, and offer you products and services you may find valuable.

We collect this information from a variety of sources including: Information we receive from you on this web site, if any; Subscription Agreements; or other forms, whether written or electronic. This information may include, but is not limited to, your name, address, social security number, and information about your level of income, net worth and investment experience. Information about your transactions with us and our affiliates or others. This information could include your use of various products or services that we and our affiliates provide. Information we receive from our affiliates. Information we receive from other third parties such as demographic firms. This information could include investment preferences. Information we receive from you online, such as cookies (small pieces of data stored by your Internet browser on your computer) or other technology that may be used to, among other things, remember passwords for you, help us track your web site usage, or provide you with customized content.

**Information we disclose**

Welton Investment Partners does not disclose any information on current or former clients or investors to any nonaffiliated third party except as permitted or required by law.

For example, we may: share information with regulatory authorities and law enforcement officials who have jurisdiction over us or if we are required to do so by United States or other applicable law; provide information to protect against fraud; share information with your prior consent; and share information with service providers that perform administrative or marketing services on our behalf or to our accountants, attorneys and auditors. In addition, we may share information about you with our affiliates as permitted by law such as information about your transactions or experiences with us, our affiliates or others. Our affiliates are financial services providers and include broker-dealers, investment advisors and fund of funds.

**Confidentiality and security procedures**

We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards in order to guard your nonpublic personal information. We restrict and limit access to nonpublic personal information about you to (a) those employees and affiliates who need to know that information to provide products or services to you; and (b) those nonaffiliated third parties whose access to such information is permitted by law and who need to know that information in order to assist us in providing you with the products and services you receive from us.  We educate and train our employees on how to properly handle personal information and safeguard customer information and prevent its unauthorized access, disclosure or use. In addition, affiliates and nonaffiliated third parties that have access to personal information must agree to follow appropriate standards of security and confidentiality.

**Changes to our privacy policy**

We may amend this policy at any time and we will inform you of changes as required by law.

If you have any questions regarding our Privacy Policy or if the information we have about you has changed, please contact us at [inquiries@welton.com](mailto:inquiries@welton.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy%20) or at (831) 626-5190.
